http://www.ruthralesjfs.org/legal_tab/#tab-2

JFS PRIVACY POLICY
JFS respects the privacy of every individual who uses JFS owned websites, mobile applications and other online products and services (collectively, "Site"). This privacy policy applies to any collection or sharing of your information, including information collected on our Site. This policy was developed to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information will not be used in any manner inconsistent with JFS’ stated privacy, fiscal management & responsibility, and organizational objectives. JFS endeavors to utilize industry standard, reasonable, and commercially feasible precautions to protect your Personally Identifiable Information.Latest Version
JFS reserves the right to revise this Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will note the date of last update at the top or bottom of this Privacy Policy.  Also please reference the separate JFS Donor Privacy Policy
Data Collection
This Site may collect standard website traffic pattern information such as the visitor's IP address, page visits
and server usage statistics. We do not collect personally identifiable information from you unless you provide it to us voluntarily and knowingly. If you request information, initiate a contact form, make a donation, register for an event, call us, or write to us, we may collect the following information: name, address, telephone number, email address, subject of inquiry, or other information specified at the time of your inquiry. If we ask for credit card or billing information,(refer to "Security" section below) we will not store this information on JFS servers or systems.
Security
We take industry standard precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via our Site, your information is protected both online and offline. Whenever we collect sensitive information (such as credit card data) on our Site, that information is encrypted and transmitted in a secure manner. You can verify this by looking for a closed lock icon at the bottom of your web browser, or looking for "https" at the beginning of the address of the web page.
We process your financial transactions securely using the Payment Card Industry Data Security Standard ("PCI DSS") (the credit card industry's most stringent security standard). Examples of our security measures include: physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards; sophisticated security monitoring tools; use of strong encryption (e.g., SSL/TLS) for transmissions of donation information to and from our credit card processor; restricted access of personally identifiable information; and periodic security audits.
In addition to protecting sensitive information transmitted online, we also protect your information offline. Only employees who need the information to perform a specific job (for example, billing or customer service) are granted access to Personally Identifiable Information. The computers/servers in which we store Personally Identifiable Information use industry standard security practices, and are kept in a secure limited-access environment. We do NOT store your credit card information on our servers.
Use & Disclosure of Information
We will not sell, trade, rent or share your Personally Identifiable Information, collected on the Site or through any other business activities, with anyone else, including any third parties, without your express permission. We will not send you mailings on behalf of other organizations without your prior request. We always provide you the opportunity to remove your name from our mailing and emailing lists, if you so choose. Send your opt-out request to info@ralesjfs.org
Demographic Information Sharing
We may collect aggregated demographic and website usage information from our Site. This is not linked to any Personally Identifiable Information that can identify any individual person. We may share this aggregated demographic and usage information with our partners and advertisers from time to time.
Cookies
We may use "cookies" on certain pages of this Site. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a website visitor's hard drive to help us improve your access to our Site and identify repeat visitors to our Site. Cookies can also enable us to track and target the interests of all our users as a group to enhance their experience on our Site. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any Personally Identifiable Information on our Site. You may choose NOT to accept cookies on most browsers, by setting options for preventing, accepting, or receiving cookies. However, please be aware that if you block cookies, some website functionality may be lost.
Links
This Site contains links to other websites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of such other websites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our Site and to read the privacy policy of any other site that may collect Personally Identifiable Information.
Questions & Contact Information
If you have any questions about JFS or our privacy policy, please feel free to contact us at:
Ruth & Norman Rales Jewish Family Services, Inc.
21300 Ruth and Baron Coleman Blvd.
Boca Raton, Florida 33428
(561) 852-3333
info@ralesjfs.org
Version June 1, 2015
JFS WEBSITE TERMS OF USE
This Internet World Wide Web site with its pages residing in the domain "ralesjfs.org", and including any and all subdomains included within that top level domain, (hereinafter the "Website") is a complimentary information and community service offered by Ruth & Norman Rales Jewish Family Services, Inc. ("JFS"), with the express condition that any and all users of this Website agree to be bound by the terms and conditions as set forth in this User Agreement. Use of this Website constitutes your acceptance of all of the included terms and conditions, in their current form or as modified. If you do not agree to these terms and conditions, you must exit this Website immediately.Latest Version
JFS reserves the right to change these terms and conditions at any time, without notice to you, and you must agree to the terms contained in the most recent version of this User Agreement (not an older or cached version) each time you view the Website.
Reasonableness
By using this Website, you agree that these Terms of Use and User Agreement, including any exclusions and limitations of liability as set forth in this Website Terms of Use are reasonable.
If you do not think these Terms are reasonable, you must not use this website.
No Warranties
This Website is provided “as is” without any representations or warranties, express or implied.
JFS, its Board members, employees, volunteers, or content providers make no representations or warranties in relation to this Website or the information and materials provided on this Website.
JFS assumes no responsibility or liability for the timeliness, deletion of information, availability of the Website, and whether or not the information on this website is complete, true, accurate or non-misleading. Nothing on this Website constitutes, or is meant to constitute, advice of any kind.
You agree that JFS shall not be liable to you or to any third party for any modification, suspension, or discontinuance of the Website.
Limitations of Liability
JFS will not be liable to you (whether under the law of contract, the law of torts or otherwise) in relation to the contents of, or use of, or otherwise in connection with, this Website, whether for any indirect, special or consequential loss, or for any business losses, loss of revenue, income, profits or anticipated income, savings, or loss, or loss of contracts or business relationships, loss of reputation or goodwill, or loss or corruption of information. You further agree that the limitations of warranties and liability set out in this Website Terms of Use will protect all JFS’ board of directors, officers, employees, agents, subsidiaries, successors, assigns and sub-contractors. These limitations of liability will apply even if JFS has been expressly advised of any potential loss or liability.
Exceptions
Nothing in this Website Terms of Use will exclude or limit any warranty implied by law that it would be unlawful to exclude or limit.
If any provision of this Website Terms of Use is, or is found to be, unenforceable under applicable law, that shall not affect the enforceability of the other provisions of this Website Terms of Use.
Indemnification
You agree to defend, indemnify and hold harmless JFS, its affiliates and their respective board of directors, officers, employees, volunteers and agents from and against all claims and expenses, including but not limited to attorneys' fees, arising out of the use of the Website by you or your designate. JFS reserves the right to take over the exclusive defense of any claim for which JFS is entitled to indemnification under this Agreement. In such event, you shall provide JFS or its agents with such cooperation as is reasonably requested by JFS.
Endorsements
You acknowledge that the opinions and recommendations contained in this Website are not necessarily those of the JFS or endorsed by JFS. JFS may provide links on the Website to other websites which are not under the control of JFS. These links are provided for convenience of reference only and are not intended as an endorsement by JFS of the organization or individual operating the website or a warranty of any type regarding the website or the information on the website.
Usage of Content
Unless otherwise expressly indicated, all information contained on this Website, such as text, graphics,
icons, images, audio, or other content, is copyrighted by and proprietary to JFS and/or other third parties, and may not be copied, reproduced, transmitted, displayed, performed, distributed, sublicensed, altered, stored for subsequent use or otherwise used in whole or in part in any manner without JFS' prior written consent, except that the user may make such temporary copies in a single computer's memory and hard drive and/or cache as are necessary to browse the website.
JFS, its parent, subsidiaries and affiliates, own all rights to their logos and trademarks used in connection with the Website. All other logos and trademarks appearing on the Website are the property of their respective owners.
Jurisdiction
This Website (excluding linked sites) is controlled by JFS which is headquartered in the State of Florida, United States of America. It can be accessed from all U.S. states, as well as from other countries around the world. As each of these places has laws that may differ from those of Florida, by accessing this Website both you and JFS agree that the statutes and laws of the State of Florida, without regard to conflicts of laws principles thereof, will apply to all matters arising from or relating to use of this Website. You and the JFS also agree and hereby submit to the exclusive personal jurisdiction and venue of the Superior Court of Palm Beach County, Florida and the United States District Court for the Southern District of Florida with respect to such matters. JFS makes no representation that materials on the Website are appropriate or available for use in other locations, and accessing them from territories where their contents are illegal is prohibited. Those who choose to access this Website from other locations do so on their own initiative and are responsible for compliance with local laws and regulations.
Version June 1, 2015
JFS DONOR PRIVACY POLICY
JFS is committed to respecting the privacy of our Donors. This privacy policy applies to any collection or sharing of Donor information, including information collected on our website. This policy was developed to ensure that your Personally Identifiable Information will not be used in any manner inconsistent with JFS’ stated privacy, fiscal management & responsibility, and organizational objectives. Every reasonable and commercially feasible precaution is taken to protect your Donor information.
Protection of Personally Identifiable Information
Personally Identifiable Information is information that identifies you personally, such as, among others, your name, address, telephone number or email address. We may collect and store the Personally Identifiable Information that you have provided us. Here are some examples of ways in which we may collect your information.
• When you request information from us via our website or otherwise contact us for information
in person, by phone or email.
• When you register for an event or attendance verified activity.
• When you make a contribution, either on our website, over the phone or by mailing in a check.
• When you sign up to receive reminder or activity notifications.
• We may collect personal information from you, from time to time, in ways not described above.
Use And Disclosure of Personally Identifiable Information
Except as described in this Donor Privacy Policy, or as described at the time we request the information from you, or with your written consent, we do not otherwise disclose your Personally Identifiable Information to any third parties.
• We will not sell, trade, rent or share your personal information, collected on the website or through
any other business activities, with anyone else.
• We will not send you mailings on behalf of other organizations without your prior request.
• We will collect payment information, billing address and other information necessary to process a
donation or event registration, or other opt-in activity.
• We may use your personal information to send you information about JFS programs, events or
annual fundraising appeals, unless you tell us not to send (opt-out).
• We provide donors with the opportunity to remove their name from our mailing and emailing lists, if so
desired, and unsubscribe information is located at the bottom of each e-Blast.
• Unless directed otherwise, we may use your personal information to acknowledge you by name and/or
description of donation in certain printed materials, such as the annual report and event invitations       or programs, or the organization’s website.
• We will use your personal information to comply with the law or regulations or in the good faith belief
that such action is necessary to conform to the requirements of law or regulation or to comply with
legal process served on us, protect and defend our rights or act in urgent instances to protect the
personal safety of others.
• We will use your personal information to protect against potential fraud. We may verify with third
parties the information collected in the course of processing a gift, event registration or other donation.
If you use a credit or debit card on the website, we may use card authorization and fraud screening
services to verify that your card information and address matches the information that you supplied to us
and that the card being used has not been reported lost or stolen.
• We have procedures in place to limit access to Personally Identifiable Information to those employees
who need to know such Personally Identifiable Information in order to fulfill our mission, and we
contractually require any person or organization providing services to JFS to protect the
confidentiality of donor information in the event they must interface with systems containing
the Personally Identifiable Information.
Latest Version
JFS reserves the right to revise this Donor Privacy Policy from time to time. When we do, we will note the date of last update at the top or bottom of this Privacy Policy.
Questions & Contact Information
If you have any questions about JFS or our Donor Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us at:
Ruth & Norman Rales Jewish Family Services, Inc.
21300 Ruth and Baron Coleman Blvd.
Boca Raton, Florida 33428
(561) 852-3333
info@ralesjfs.org
Version June 1, 2015
home
about us
our mission
location/directions
Phone: (561) 558-2100
Copyright ©2020 Ruth & Norman Rales JFS, 501(c)(3) Nonprofit EIN: 65-1115689 | Privacy Policy | Terms Of Use | Donor Privacy Policy |
Site Map
Contributions benefit Ruth & Norman Rales Jewish Family Services, Inc., a not-for-profit, tax-exempt organization. A COPY OF THE OFFICIAL REGISTRATION AND FINANCIAL INFORMATION MAY BE OBTAINED FROM THE DIVISION OF CONSUMER SERVICES AT www.FloridaConsumerHelp.com OR BY CALLING TOLL-FREE (800-435-7352) WITHIN THE STATE. REGISTRATION DOES NOT IMPLY ENDORSEMENT, APPROVAL, OR RECOMMENDATION BY THE STATE. Registration #CH13203
